Hello hello welcome to my channel gas i hope
you guys are fine today in this video we are going to
talk about
what is the cost of the scooter parts and I read this in some people's
comments on Twitter and in the
electric group of Facebook
that my scooter fell, my scooter
got scratched or its back
cover is damaged or broken so
how much will it cost you to get it repaired
so see gas you get two types of options
one is that you can do it on end basis
what will that pet message do for you
so for that thing stay tuned to this video
I will give you further information
you will attach this screenshot in this
video in which you will be able to
see the prices of the parts and apart from that the
other option is to make an insurance claim
so if the cost of your scooter
is high then only make this insurance claim now
but if
your cost is up to 10000 rupees then you
can also get it done on pet basis the twist is
yours gets done quickly now if you make an insurance claim then
you have to give some time for that
I worked for 9 to 10 days and
made a video related to this, you
can go and check it in my playlist,
what is the way in which you can claim insurance,
so this video is only for the
purpose that if you want to get something done on this, then from
where will you get the list of licenses, so
I have collected that
price for you, you can
see it in the description of the video as well and you
can also see it on the screen that will appear above, so
what is there in this, guys, if you want to get it done on pet basis, then
first of all
you have to get it done, at the time of your stay, the
service center which is near you
calls you, after calling,
when the engineer visits you here, then the
engineer tells you the price of the parts etc. and
tells you that after all, it will
cost you so much, or it may be that
Vodafone itself tells you that these are the
prices for this part and if you want to get the scooter repaired then first of all
you will make the
payment and then after that whatever  If there is an
engineer or technician, he will
come here with that part or if it is nearby,
like I am in Delhi, then there
is Patparganj near me, Jogging is
about 15 kilometers from here, so
you can physically
go there and get all these things done, so that's all
in this video and if
you liked it then like and
subscribe and share it with your friends,
I am back